Okay. Manuel, right?
This for you.
It's 25 for the vehicle
and 30 for the transport
of the livestock.
Just put down "one horse"
and your signature right there.
You said "one horse"?
Yeah, it's only one,
right?
No, it's an elephant.
You mean
"really big horse"?
No. I mean an elephant.
Look, sir...
...the call said "one--"
Whoa...
What the fuck
is that?
Holy shit!
Is that a fucking elephant?
Señor, señor, señor.
Probablemente it was some kind
of bad communication.
Bad communication?
This is a truck
for fucking horses, man!
What do I look like,
a goddamn maharaja?
All right.
And you're invited
to the party.
More gas!
Come on. Come on!
Give me--
Fuck! Fuck!
Goddamn it!
Motherfucker!
Good evening, Officer.
What exactly
is going on here?
Um, well, we're--
I work for Don Wallach,
and we're transporting
the entertainment
for a party at his house.
That's an elephant.
Yes, sir.
You got a permit?
Um, I didn't know
we needed one.
Can't drive an elephant
without a permit.
Could you make
an exception?
How's the guest list
looking for tonight?
It's impressive.
Hmm.
What kind of stars
are we talking about?
Someone said Garbo,
I think.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. I mean,
that's what I heard.
So, we're talking an elephant,
plus Garbo,
plus others tonight
at Don Wallach's house,
is that right?
That's right.
Sounds like
the best party in town.
My cousin Benny lives in Reseda
with his wife and kids.
I'll see if they're free.
Who the fuck
are all these people?
♪ One, two, three, hey ♪
Does Piggy like that?
It tickles.
Playtime with potty time!
José! José!
Can you ask Wallach
to give us more King Bubbly,
por favor?
Okay.
Would you mind showing me
to the upstairs powder room,
my dear boy?
Sure. Uh, it's here
down the hall.
No!
No, no, upstairs.
The stairs are very steep,
I think.
I can be carried.
Evening, Madame.
Lovely to see you.
I have to steal him, I'm afraid.
What did you say to Elinor?
Who?
Elinor St. John.
Never speak to her.
If she ever talks to you again,
pretend like you don't
understand English.
The chicken
stole my fucking coke!
Go fucking get it! Get it!
Give it to me!
So, upstairs is where Don keeps
his underage girls, then?
Well, that came out
of fucking nowhere.
You'll have to pay
for that, ma'am.
Oh. Okay.
Uh, who are you?
I'm security.
You're kind of shitty
at your job.
You have statues
coming out of nowhere,
everywhere you fucking turn.
You're very lucky
I don't report you.
Where do you think
you're going, ma'am?
I'm going inside.
I'm Nellie LaRoy,
dummy.
There's no "Nellie LaRoy"
on the list.
Okay, well, I think--
Come here.
I think what's happened
is my assistant has put me
under my stage name,
Billie Dove.
You're not Billie Dove.
Okay,
what the fuck is your prob--
What is your name?
What is your precinct?
I'm a security guard.
We don't have precincts, ma'am.
You're about
to not have a job, fucko!
Listen, I know you wish
you were Billie Dove--
I think you wish
you were eating my asshole!
Nellie LaRoy?
They're waiting for you.
I'm Manuel.
I heard ya.
Oh, I didn't need
your help.
Oh, no?
Nope.
Billie Dove?
Why not?
She's kind of a big star.
Well, in 30 years
she won't be a big star anymore
and she can tell her grandkids
Nellie LaRoy once used her name.
Besides,
I'm already a star.
Ah, you are?
Yeah.
What have you been in?
Nothing yet.
Who's your contract with?
Don't have one.
Okay, I think you want
to become a star.
Honey, you don't become a star.
You either are one or you ain't.
I am.
Oh, great.
Do you know where
I can find some drugs?
We're supposed
to just keep playing?
That's the idea.
It's gonna come
through the front and
just kind of stomp around.
Are you serious?
Just stay
out of its way.
You know I can't afford
to get injured, Joe.
Will you shut the fuck up?
What?
You heard me,
you whiny bitch.
Excuse me?
Come on, you guys.
You see how
he just talks to me?
I talk to you like this
because every time we play
in these,
you playing fucking flat.
If that elephant
drop its elephant ass
on your face,
maybe you'd be home long enough
to fucking practice.
I practice nine hours a day,
you fuck.
Yeah, yeah,
but I mean on saxophone,
not cocksucking.
I don't have fucking time
for this!
Wake up, wake up, wake up!
What a goddamn mess.
We were just having fun!
Tell it to Wallach.
Wake up, wake up.
Where's the Mexican?
Morphine, opium, ether,
heroin, coke.
And Louis XIV
sat on that.
...pretend
that everything's fine inside
when all I feel is this void.
And all I do is I give
and I give!
Pedro!
And you, I don't even know,
where are you?
Where are you?
Stop speaking
fucking Italian!
No. No, it's not.
I'm trying to have
a serious conversation with you.
Do you understand?
Our marriage is in trouble.
I am unhappy!
Stop it!
You are not fucking Italian!
You are from
fucking Shawnee,
you goddamn fraud!
Say one more word.
Say one more word in Italian,
and I will divorce you.
One more.
Okay. Okay.
Get the fuck out!
Get the fuck
out of the car! Go!
Ah! Hey!
Get out! Go!
I want a divorce.
Morning, Dale.
Evening, Mr. Conrad.
Evening.
- Jack! Jack!
- Oh, my God! J.C.!
Natalie!
It's been forever!
Yeah.
I've been saying it
since Wally Reid.
Who needs royalty anymore?
Madame.
Dearest Jacky boy,
we need to talk!
I have a good story for you.
I have your face
tattooed on my back.
Well, look at that.
Jack, for fuck's sake,
I've been trying you all week.
Will you just
fucking call me back?
Come here, you moola-minting
money machine motherfucker!
Jack, is it okay to grab one?
Hey, Charlie.
How's the missus?
I think she left me.
Hey, me too! Congrats!
Are you okay with March 17th
for the premiere?
No, 18th. Thursdays
are always classier.
Hey, send Charlie
a bottle of bourbon
and get ahold of his negative
and make sure I don't
look too shiny.
Yes, Mr. Conrad.
No Mrs. Conrad tonight?
Mmm.
Mm-mmm.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I think we have a problem.
We do?
Yep.
This table only has one bottle,
and we're gonna need eight.
We're also gonna need
two gin rickeys,
an orange blossom with brandy,
three French 75s.
Can you do a Corpse Reviver?
Gin, lemon,
triple sec and Kina Lillet
with a dash of absinthe.
Two of those.
Okay. Two gin rickeys,
uh, three French--
You didn't have to do that,
you know, to get my attention.
I am so sorry,
Mr. Conrad.
I want--
What's your name?
Jen. I just wanted you
to look my way.
Jen, I'd always look your way.
Sir, George won't
come out of the car.
He's insisting I drive him
off the nearest cliff.
Right.
Be right back.
She said no, huh?
After all we've been through.
Well, to be fair, George,
you did just meet her
a week ago.
What we had was special,
goddamn it.
I know, buddy,
but you're not gonna
kill yourself over it.
Save the ring
and come on inside.
There's a girl
asking after ya.
Yeah?
That's right.
There you go,
buddy.
Who's the girl?
A goddess.
No Paris for me.
I'm good.
What?
You've never done cocaine?
Of course I've done cocaine.
Well?
I do cocaine all the time.
I just, uh...
Don't make me
do it alone.
Okay, I'll do a little.
Whatever.
I don't care.
I don't know,
maybe Niagara Falls.
You know, "Roy," actually,
in French, means "king."
And I added the "La,"
so it's "Nellie the King."
I made that up.
What about you?
Where would you go?
Sorry?
If you could go
anywhere in the whole world,
where would you go?
Uh, anywhere.
I don't know. Um...
I always wanted to go
on a movie set.
Yeah?
Yeah. A movie set.
Tell me why.
Why?
Yeah, tell me why.
All right, um...
I don't know why.
I wanna go on a movie set too.
Why? I just want to be part
of something bigger, I guess.
Bigger than what?
Bigger than this.
Bigger than my life.
Bigger than scooping
elephant shit.
Bigger. Better. Important.
Something important.
To be part
of something important.
Something that lasts,
that means something.
I love that answer.
Making movies.
I want to go
on a movie set too.
Or at least I want to be there,
work there, learn there.
I don't know.
I just love watching movies,
you know?
I love watching movies too.
You sit there.
And you're watching
the movie and--
And you escape.
You don't have to be
in your own shitty fucking life.
Exactly! Exactly!
You can be in their life.
Or wherever!
You can be
in the fucking Wild West!
You can be in fucking space!
You can be like a gangster.
And people dance in movies
and people die in movies.
And they're not really dead.
It's fucking amazing.
They're not really dead.
Like literally, kill me.
Pow!
And nothing happened, for real,
but at the same time,
it's something
even more important than life.
You can feel it.
Like-- I don't know.
Movies are sad sometimes.
Movies are fucking happy.
They make you feel something.
One day, you and me,
we're gonna be on a movie set.
We can have lunch together.
Yeah, for sure.
I don't know what
I'm going to do yet.
It'll be just you and me.
Yeah, you and me.
Yeah.
You know,
you're not bad-looking.
Thank you.
And now, the Rose Petal...
...of the Rising Sun--
Miss Lady Fay Zhu!
Shh.
♪ There's one pet
I like to pet ♪
♪ Every evening we get set ♪
♪ I stroke it
Every chance I get ♪
♪ It's my girl's ♪
♪ Pussy ♪
♪ Seldom plays and never purrs ♪
♪ And I love
The thoughts it stirs ♪
♪ But I don't mind
Because it's hers ♪
♪ It's my girl's pussy ♪
♪ 'Cause I'll do anything
For my sweet pet ♪
♪ She works me to a sweat ♪
♪ And that's hard to do ♪
♪ I must first
Remove my gloves ♪
♪ When stroking my girl's ♪
♪ Pussy ♪
Lady Fay, Lady Fay, come stai?
Fine. Didn't get the part,
but writing the titles on it.
I'm stuck doing
another costume picture,
and my wife's divorcing me.
Want to trade?
No.
Eh...
That woman is something,
you know?
She was completely
honest with me.
Your wife?
God, no. My--
Jen. The, uh...
Ah.
Listen, I need a favor.
You know my old friend
George over there?
I wonder
if you'd go talk to him.
Tell him you were
asking after him.
That sad man over there?
Yeah.
Listen, I'm not asking you
to fuck him.
Just, you know,
make him...
...feel special.
Hmm?
Okay.
Don't speak Cantonese to me.
All right.
Oh, I love this song!
You! I've been looking
all over for you.
We got a serious
fucking situation.
There's no exit except
down the main staircase.
Nothing in the back?
No.
You gotta go
through the ballroom.
Everyone will see her.
Is there a doctor?
No.
They're all high down there.
Maybe they won't care.
If we take her out now--
Somebody will care!
She's a fucking kid,
and she looks like she's dead.
We use the elephant.
We bring him
through the front.
Everyone will look at him.
No one will look at her.
It's only 2:00.
Don wanted to save the elephant.
Fine. Get the wrangler.
Jimmy, you carry the girl
with me. Then you drive her
to the hospital.
Doubt she'll be able
to work tomorrow.
That's her fucking problem.
No. She's in the bar scene
in Maid's Off.
Yeah.
Jane Thornton, that's her.
Bar shoots tomorrow,
doesn't it?
Yes.
Who the fuck invited her?
Um...
I did.
You blimp motherfucker,
piece of fat fucking shit!
It was her first film.
She wanted to celebrate.
I'll fucking--
You doughboy!
You fuckhead
motherfucking Humpty Dumpty!
Bob, come on! Bob!
I'm gonna cut you up!
No, Bob! Don't leave me!
Fuck!
Her.
Whoever she is.
We go with her tomorrow.
What the fuck?
Come on! Come on, baby!
Right here!
I'm right here!
Yeah. All right, Kapitän.
Just one more drink
for old time's sake.
Sir?
I just want to say
thank you for the work.
And I was wondering
if perhaps, next time,
you or Mr. Wallach
might have something
for me on a set?
I'll do anything.
I can paint, I can cook,
I can clean, I can do coffee--
You're where you belong.
Okay. Thank you.
Ooh. I'm gonna raise you.
You need to be on set in three hours.
You'd better get some sleep.
Gentlemen.
You have a good night, Nellie.
Congratulations.
Manny!
Ain't life grand?
Oh,
if they could see me now!
All the cunts in Lafayette
called me the ugliest mutt
in the neighborhood.
Well, let them see me now!
Can you believe this, Manny?
Hey, Josie! Hey, Nana!
Why don't you kiss
my royal Angeleno hooch?
Nellie.
Night night, honey.
Don't worry about that.
The car is not mine.
Chico. Hey, Chico!
Jack Conrad's
passed out.
Use one of Wallach's cars
to take him home.
Señor? Sir?
Uh, do you have keys?
Yeah. I have keys.
Damn it.
Ah, musica. Musica?
Huh?
Sì. Sì.
Imagine me at the opera?
That would've made
Ina's folks happy.
Well, if you'll excuse me...
See my point? Come on.
Ina's mom always said,
"I don't see
how you can marry someone
who paints his face."
You know what we gotta do?
We gotta redefine the form.
The man who puts gasoline
in your tank goes
to the movies why?
Why? Why?
Because he feels
less alone there.
Don't we owe him more
than the same old shit?
You got the guys in Europe
with the twelve-tone.
You got Bauhaus architecture.
Fucking Bauhaus, you know?
And we're still doing
costume pictures?
It's the dinosaurs, kid.
It's the ones
who go to Beverly Hills
for meatballs
and mint juleps
to reminisce
about the old days,
when they can't see
there's so much more to be done!
We've got to innovate.
We've got to inspire.
We got to dream beyond
these pesky shells
of flesh and bone.
Map those dreams onto celluloid
and print them into history.
Turn today into tomorrow
so that tomorrow's lonely man
may look up
at that flickering screen
and say
for the very first time,
"Eureka! I am not alone!"
Yeah.
And I'm going to bed.
Hey, where'd you go?
You need something?
Yeah, I like you.
I want you to take me
to set today.
I want you by my side.
You okay with that?
Sí.
You ever been
on a movie set before?
No.
You'll see.
It's the most magical place
in the world.
Liu?
Hole in shirt before.
No, hole not
in shirt before,
you fucking coolie!
I don't want
a fucking discount! I--
Are you...
I am.
Morning!
Time to go make a movie.
Maid's Off?
Yeah.
Come with me.
Higher! More!
Now go over, put it in the pot.
Scream like a big, fat pig.
All right. All right,
all right! Yes!
Go!
More whiskey! More whiskey!
Well, don't just
fucking stand there!
Get the fuck out of the shot!
Peanuts! Good for hangovers!
You. You're new?
You're new here?
Your first bag is free.
One bag or two? One.
And you're paying this time?
Thank you.
Hurry the fuck up!
Can you stop drinking?
We are not shooting yet!
Put down the fucking glasses!
Who the fuck is this?
I asked for the girl
with the tits.
This is who they found.
What happened
to the tits part?
She OD'd.
Just go. Just go.
Get her made up.
Max!
Yes.
Just, uh, shoot the men
or something.
No tits?
No tits.
All right, no tits, everybody!
We're shooting the men.
Diese Scheißen fucks!
They are ruining my movie!
I want them on camera
in five minutes!
Otto, please, please.
Jack's arriving.
What about pancakes?
Do you heat the syrup
or do you let the pancake
do the warming?
Heat the syrup?
I agree!
Ha. That there
is George Munn,
best producer in the biz
and my oldest pal.
Set patrol over there
is Jim Kidd.
Legend of the Wild West
who made his name
killing Apaches.
- Lives in Brentwood now.
- This is bullshit!
Georgie, what's up
Von Cheeseburger's ass today?
The extras want to
renegotiate their pay.
...you motherfucker!
Huh.
I do not care
if the extras are revolting!
Well, put the kid on it.
The kid?
Yeah, the kid.
The Mexican I brought.
He's great.
What's your name?
- Me? Manuel.
- Bullshit!
Right, Manuel.
Manuel's great!
Put Manuel on it.
You have experience
with strikes?
Um... yes.
Okay, good.
Well, these are all junkies
from Skid Row,
- so they're pretty violent.
- ...you fucking assholes!
Who are you?
That's the cocksucker
they sent to screw us!
Gentlemen, I believe
you all agreed to a day's work.
And I believe I agreed
to ram this knife
up the asshole
of the first faggot
they sent over!
This is where you kiss
the apparition, ja?
Ja.
She has led you
to your destiny
through fate,
through your lifetime
to this moment, ja?
Mm-hmm.
Very good, ja?
Ja.
I'm gonna play it adagio.
You know, for the music
and the poetry.
All art aspires to music.
I like it.
Yeah.
Sandwich!
What is this dolly
doing here?
Sir! Sir, sir!
Sir, can I borrow that?
All right, you motherfuckers!
Any of you don't work
gets a bullet
in the fucking skull!
Get back to work!
Manuel's great!
How's that for camera?
Much better, Ruth.
Jesus Christ!
Is somebody
gonna fix her face?
Get her out of here!
Fuck's sake.
Do you not know
how to do makeup?
You, what's your name?
Tim.
Tim, you're fired.
What?
You heard her!
Get the fuck off this set!
Action!
"Marbled meadows
metamorphose
into the medieval plains
of Iberia.
Soldiers swarm the fields
like flecks of paint
from a madman's brush
as your humble servant
bears witness
to the latest
of the moving picture's
magic tricks."
Oh, why do I bother?
Look at these idiots!
I knew Proust, you know.
H-He's dead.
He did have
a drinking problem.
That's true.
Probably ran into it
himself, huh?
It's a disease.
Your coffee,
Mr. Thalberg.
Gracias.
Close with Swanson
and the fireworks. The end!
Irv!
For the Clayton movie...
Sir, I-I think your tent's
in the line of fire.
They'll edit it out in post.
But I think
we could get hurt--
Jack, every time you wear
a prosthetic, we lose money.
Don't be a pussy, Irv.
The fireworks shot
is too expensive.
And you'll never
get Gloria Swanson.
Why no Swanson?
She only does leads.
She's on the phone, sir.
Thanks, Abby.
Who?
Gloria Swanson.
What?
Gloria? Jack Conrad.
Listen, I need some advice.
You know all
the young up-and-comers.
Well, I need a real discovery
for the part in my movie.
Who do you suggest?
Why discovery?
Well, this role requires
real range.
A range I just don't see
in any of today's stars--
Excuse me.
Props needs
better aging, goddamn it!
We talked about this!
Sorry, what-- No, I didn't--
Gloria, you have
buckets of charm.
This is real drama
we're talking about.
Shakespeare-level stuff.
Hmm. Of course
you could do Shakespeare.
You would be spectacular
in one of his fluffier plays.
Gloria, you're taking this
the wrong way.
Well, I'd like to work
with you too.
No, I'm afraid it's impossible.
It's gotta be a discovery.
We couldn't afford star fees
even if we wanted to.
Really? Huh.
Well, how about
I talk it over with the studio?
I can't speak for them,
of course, but I'll do my best.
Okay, then. Bye now.
She'll do it for cheap.
Now take the money I saved you
and put it towards
the goddamn fireworks shot.
Cut!
These fucking horses!
Motherfuckers!
Is that the last one?
What happened?
We lost all ten cameras.
But what about Jack's scene?
We make a camera run
right now!
It's too far!
Sun sets in three hours!
Send Joey now.
Tell him to speed.
In the meantime--
Joey has a flag sticking
through his chest, Larry.
A flag?
He ran into it himself.
Right. Um, send Miguel then.
Here. 1312 Cahuenga.
You give 'em that card,
you tell 'em you work for Munn.
And hurry!
Okay, here's the shot.
Flirt with the men. Dance.
Get up on the table
and that's it.
Just, uh, don't look
at the fucking camera.
Places!
And camera!
And music!
Action!
Hi, boys.
Santa, get me wet.
Another, please.
That one's for you,
snuggle pup.
Hey, baby grand.
Where are you going?
Uh... okay,
start dancing, please.
Bauhaus.
You know what I mean
by Bauhaus, don't you?
Not as it relates
to this, sir, no.
And then he says,
"Hasta la vista, motherfucker."
Type it.
And then he says,
"Frankly, Scarlett,
you're a cunt."
Type it.
Cut!
Man number three,
I can see your erection.
All right, tuck it.
Just tuck it up.
Hi. I work
for Mr. George Munn.
We need a camera
for Strassberger's show.
Oh, yeah?
What kind of camera?
Bell and Howell 35 millimeter.
Uh-huh.
Is it a 2708 model or 2709?
I-I'm not sure.
Is there a big difference?
Um, yeah.
Hey, Donny!
What?
There's a guy up here
wants to know
if there's a big difference
between a 2708 and a 2709.
Okay.
Do you have either?
Nope.
Every camera's
been loaned out.
Fuck.
One's coming back
in half an hour though.
Half hour?
But it's a 2709.
Yeah. Okay.
Thirty minutes.
For the 2709.
I can do that.
Thirty minutes.
Two-seven...
Okay.
...zero-nine.
Are you married?
My wife died.
Oh, I'm dreadfully sorry.
Hey! Next part.
Miss Moore'll come in.
She saved you from prostitution,
so when you see her,
cry in shame.
I need big tears!
Big! You got it?
Okay, yeah.
Is that gum?
Are you fucking kidding me?
What's wrong with you?
Five-minute warning
for Miss Moore!
That's mine!
I have 20 minutes
to be in Simi Valley.
Which road do I take?
Uh, you're gonna look
at least 90 in this traffic.
We've got an eight-part
sign-out process.
Let me go try to find a pen.
Action!
And action, Miss Moore.
Hand on chest. Aghast!
My goodness,
what is going on here?
Girl on bar,
look at Miss Moore.
And tears!
Okay, glycerin.
Um, we seem to be out.
What? We haven't used any.
Porky thought it was lube.
He thought it was lube?
Yes.
Are you fucking--
She can't cry.
She's just some random whore
from Wallach's house!
Cut.
Hiya. I'm Nellie LaRoy.
So we going again?
Fucking motherfucker.
I'm so sorry, God.
You gave us the beautiful light,
and I squandered it.
I won't have
any fucking light now.
Otto, you should have fought
for 20 cameras, you idiot!
What is this bullshit?
Camera! Camera!
Camera!
Yeah.
Camera! Camera!
My camera's here!
We roll, we roll!
We are losing the light!
Take two! Action!
And cry.
Cut! Okay, I want
to try something.
Think you could
hold for two beats
for tears gushing?
Eyes water for two,
on the third beat,
I'm gonna do a light effect.
That's when you gush.
Water for two, gush on three.
Yep.
Yes. Okay, let's do it!
Ruth, any notes on my entrance?
You're fine.
Ready for you, Mr. Conrad.
Action!
Eyes water.
Light. And tears!
Cut!
Okay. Forgive the ask.
This is nuts.
But could you, by any chance,
try the same thing
with less tears?
One tear or two?
Let's do this.
'Twas brillig
and the slithy toves were...
Oh, hey. Come with.
Camera's up the hill,
Mr. Conrad.
Over here?
There? Yeah.
We'd better hurry.
There? Okay.
Ah, my beautiful baby boy.
Come, come.
Okay, right here.
Now remember,
you are sad and lonely man.
Right here.
No one will ever love you
but her, and she's only
in your head, okay?
Last looks!
Do I know her?
No. She's in your head!
No, no! No last looks!
No last looks!
Get the fuck out!
I'll fucking kill you!
We are losing the light!
We roll now! We roll!
Roll, roll, roll, roll.
Music!
And action.
Action!
Oh, my God, it's a fire!
Everyone, run!
Run!
Don't stop the camera!
Keep rolling! Keep rolling!
Single tear!
Cannon!
More crying!
Now laugh
in embarrassment.
Now look at Miss Moore.
You're trying
to hide the shame.
Hold steady.
What the--
You're trying
to be strong.
to bury the pain.
But you can't hold back
that one final tear!
And cut.
Cut.
We got it.
Who the fuck is that?
Camera boy! The camera boy!
You saved my movie!
I love you! I love you!
Yes! Did you see that?
Did you see the butterfly?
That was a butterfly.
Who's writing
the titles on this?
I gotta ask you something.
Yeah? Was it okay?
It was incredible!
I just-- How do you do it?
Just tear up over and over
like it's nothing?
I just think of home.
So, Jacky boy,
how do you think it turned out?
Ah, people want the kiss,
we give them the kiss.
But, madame,
I can't help but wonder,
don't we have
a higher calling?
We got a lot of great stuff.
We're really excited
about our new discovery,
Nellie LaRoy.
Is she here tonight?
Can you point her out to me?
Uh...
Yeah, she's the one having sex
with the ice sculpture.
We're all very fond of her.
It needs more punch.
Take two frames off the tail
and three more off the head.
Manuel.
Yes?
I saw Olga Putti sing
to herself in Hungarian,
and I think I'm in love.
Send two dozen roses
to her dressing room
every morning this week.
You know she doesn't
speak English?
Neither does love.
Let's do a title here.
"I've been
in fashion shows too.
They voted me
the 'Least Dressed Woman'
in Paris."
And when it looks like the guy
asks her something,
have him ask her name
and have her reply,
"No names.
Just call me the wild child."
Do you think
she swings both ways?
You're not on the list.
Okay, listen to me.
My name is Nellie LaRoy.
Still not on the list.
Lady, I'm in the movie.
They clearly cut you, baby.
Is that snakeskin?
Oh, my God! Nellie LaRoy!
Can I have an autograph?
I once fought
a rattlesnake,
and it's against the law to
even deal with a rattlesnake.
Gorgeous! Gorgeous!
There are laws now
because I fought
the rattlesnake and lived.
Okay. You can go in.
Why, thank you.
Naturally, I always knew
my daughter had it in her.
We're gonna do great things
together, she and I.
By the way,
the name is Robert Roy.
She added the "La."
It's celebration time
for Jack Conrad.
The epic Blood & Gold
has confirmed Jack
as the highest-grossing
leading man in the world.
And now he's got his nuptials
to toast,
this time
with the Hungarian vixen,
Olga Putti.
One unlucky girl who did not
attend the festivities:
a Kansas teenager who,
overcome by the combined effect
of Valentino's death
and Conrad's fifth betrothal,
slit her wrists at home.
How sad.
Meanwhile, that new favorite,
Nellie LaRoy,
is making other girls
with California dreams
Roy-ally jealous!
Kinoscope's reteaming
the firecracker from Jersey
with Constance Moore.
And you know what that means:
"Moore" delightful chemistry
with Constance and Nellie!
This goddamn bitch
is stealing the scene
right from under me!
She's changing the blocking
with every take.
She's icing her nipples
so they perk up
through her dress.
Fuck you.
I ain't icing my nipples.
This is natural.
You're just sore because
yours look like fucking latkes.
And she placed this
in my dressing room.
I don't even know
what that is.
Oh!
Guys, let's just try
a take, okay? I don't think
she meant anything by it.
Let's go back
to our ones.
I need a drink. Whore!
Nellie, back to your one.
Guys, back to your one.
I'll give you something
to cry about!
All right, we're going again!
Action!
Whoo!
Stop! She's changed
the blocking again!
Fine. Grab a close-up.
No! No close-up.
To match-cut with yours.
I'm the star!
I get the close-up.
This is my money.
My company's writing the checks.
I decide!
Fine.
Close-up on Constance.
Close-up on Constance!
Hi, Dr. Lubin.
I think I want to get
that operation we discussed.
Tonight.
Oh, my God.
How long
will that take to heal?
What do you say we come in
for my close-up now?
"Common and uncouth
though she may be,
there's something about her
that speaks to us in a language
as vital and as bracing
as life itself."
All right, you heard her.
Close-up on Nellie.
"Never have I seen
such a maelstrom of bad taste
and sheer magic.
Your humble servant
bears witness.
She has killed
our grandmothers,
and we thank her for it!"
How much?
Jack!
It's Billy. Remember?
Yeah. Hi.
You should
come by the Warners lot.
Haven't seen you there
in a while.
Yeah.
Jolson's sound picture's
real good.
Sound picture?
Yeah.
Like Don Juan?
No, no, no, no. Singing.
Talking pictures.
Like you're there.
Not like the shorts.
Really?
Yeah. It's wild.
We did a screening
on the lot last week.
People went nuts.
You, uh, think people
want that, though?
Sound in their movies?
Yeah,
why wouldn't they?
This is what
we've been looking for!
Sound is how
we redefine the form.
Sound!
Sweetie, I don't--
I don't know
what you're upset about.
I don't understand Hungarian.
I heard Warners'
screening last week
was a train wreck.
Manuel, what's she saying?
I got him learning Hungarian
'cause he's good with languages.
Something about "getting fucked
by a wheelbarrow of monkeys."
Hiccups are normal.
Geez Louise!
Olga? Does this mean you
don't like the rain machine
I made you?
She missed the rain in Budapest
so I built a rain machine
in the garden.
Hiccups that last ten years?
Manuel?
Something about...
Took ten years for
the Wrights' airplane to work.
...a horse's cock
and your anus.
Didn't it?
That's not the same thing.
That's not the same.
Didn't it? Aha! Why not?
Progress comes in fits.
Hello?
Spurts and fits.
Thalberg.
People go to movies
not to listen to the noise.
Irv?
Jack.
I wanna know about
the Al Jolson movie.
Get Manuel to New York.
Send him to the Warners' Theatre
to see the premiere
and have him report back.
Jolson? All right.
Who is that screaming?
That's just Olga.
Look, don't stand
in the way of progress, Irv.
Sound is the future.
Whoa! Hey! Holy shit!
Send Manuel to New York.
- Jack! Jack, get down!
- Sweetie, sweetie.
Is this about Greta?
You know she's just a friend.
Get down! Jack!
♪ For the longest while ♪
What the fuck was that?
Hello? Hello?
Jack? Jack?
- Jack?
- Nellie!
I got the ticket
to the premiere.
Nellie! Nellie, I love you!
I know.
I'll let you know how it is.
Nellie! Nellie!
Yes, Jack.
Yeah, okay. Bye.
Please, Nellie!
Nellie, please
can I have your autograph?
Nellie! Nellie!
Nellie!
Manny!
Please, Nellie!
Show me your tits,
you fucking bitch!
Right here!
Stop, stop, stop!
You fucking whore!
I love you.
No, no, no!
Back off, cabrones!
Back off now!
Nellie!
Tony, go, go!
How you been?
Eh, good, good.
Ah! Look at you!
Wow.
You remember me.
Yeah, of course
I remember you.
How could I forget?
And you're a star now.
I was always a star,
remember?
Right, right.
And, um,
what are you doing here?
Are you here for a movie or...
No, I had to get out of town
for a few days.
Some shit came up with a guy
saying I owed him money
in a game of craps.
Then Wallach got pissed.
He straightened him out.
But he thinks
I have a gambling problem,
which I don't.
I only gamble if I'm,
you know, pissed or drunk
or having a great night.
What about you?
Um, Jack Conrad sent me.
Jack Conrad?
Yeah, I'm working
with him.
Oh! I would fuck him.
Wow.
Why would Conrad
send you here? God.
I got out of this place
first chance I got.
Took nothing with me
but my dad.
He's actually
my business manager now.
He is?
Yeah. He's so bad at it.
Cannot add, cannot spell.
Why don't you hire
someone else?
He's my dad.
What else is he gonna do?
Oh, shit, we're here.
Hey, Tony?
Can you hang onto this
for me, please? Thanks.
I'm just gonna
be a minute, okay?
Actually, uh, do you wanna
come in with me?
Yeah.
May I help you?
Yes. Nellie LaRoy.
Hi.
Seems okay here.
It's pretty nice.
This is Manny.
He works
in the movies too.
Okay. Thank you.
That was a waste of time.
Let's go.
I hate when people
put fucking toppings
on ice cream.
Doesn't need it.
It messes up a good thing.
You know what I mean?
I fucking hate that.
God, I've never done nothing
except disappoint people
my whole life.
Teachers told me I was no good.
Boys told me I was no good.
Every fucking casting director
in the city told me
I was too short
or I was too fat.
Usually I was too fat.
You know, my mama actually
had some fat years too.
You wouldn't know it now,
looking at her, but she did.
They fucked up with me, Manny.
They really fucked up with me.
'Cause I make 'em squirm.
And I like
making 'em squirm.
Let 'em know that I got here
on my terms, not theirs.
And when I'm done,
I'm gonna dance my ass off
into the night.
And they'll know--
everyone will fucking know
that they could never control
one goddamn fucking thing.
Do you like ice cream?
Of course.
My family lives in LA,
you know.
Really?
I thought
they were in Mexico.
We crossed the border
when I was 12.
They're not far.
I could take a car,
drive for 30 minutes
and just say hi.
But you never do.
Sí.
It's just easier
to be on my own.
I've always been on my own.
Um, Tony, take Manny
wherever he needs to go.
Oh, no, it's okay.
No, no, no.
I insist. I insist.
I'm gonna see you
back in LA, okay?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Jack? It's Manny.
Everything's about to change.
Nell, how you feeling?
I'm ready.
Yeah, you gonna
try a take?
Yeah.
Okay, so we're
gonna pre-roll first.
I'll cue your entrance.
First mark is where
you say the line,
"Hello, college,"
and then you head to the phone,
do the rest of the dialogue.
Sounds easy.
I think it will be.
Lloyd,
any direction on voice?
Uh, no, we're good
up here, Ruth.
Okay, great.
Uh, Mark,
can we fix her makeup?
Mark.
No air conditioning?
It's too loud.
Okay.
Just be natural.
You'll be fine.
All right,
places, everyone!
Uh, hey, whoa, what is that?
Harry, what kind of shoes
are those?
Uh...
Come on, guys,
rubber soles!
Okay, everyone, a reminder.
Rubber soles only
from now on!
Okay.
And camera! And sound!
"It's Joanne
from 31 Grimes Hall.
I just--"
Fuck! "31 Grays Hall."
Grays Hall, Grays Hall.
"Hiya, this is Joanne
from 31 Grays Hall.
I just wanted to see
if the phone worked."
"Just wanted to see
if the phone worked.
Who is this?"
- Scene 17, take one.
- Mark.
Come on. Come on, come on.
You know it.
And action!
Hello, college!
Jesus, fuck! Cut!
What happened?
She blew the valves.
- I just need a minute.
- All right, well, hurry.
Give me one sec.
Christ,
it's hot in there.
Okay, are we still in places?
Okay.
Okay, all set here.
Miss LaRoy?
Yeah.
What would really help us
would be if you said the line
a little more quietly.
- Okay.
-  All right, places, everyone!
And camera!
And sound!
Close that!
Don't you know
what a red light means?
Scene 17, take two.
Mark.
Action.
Cut.
Missed your mark, Nell.
- Oh.
- It's...
Yeah, I, uh...
I don't know, I felt,
like, a little lighter
on my feet that time.
I feel I should come
further into the room.
Right, but the microphone is...
Um--
All right. Hey, Lloyd?
Yeah.
Can we just move the mic
a little deeper in the room?
Why?
Because Nellie felt
lighter on her feet that time.
I was just saying
I think I should come
further into the room.
Oh, okay. Yeah, sure,
I mean, if you have
half an hour to spare.
Half an hour?
Well, I can't just move the mic.
I have to redo
all the wires.
We'll have to reset the rafters,
then find the new position.
Then I'm gonna have to
recalibrate the whole room.
Okay, okay. Okay.
Nell, why don't we just--
Is it okay--
Let's just try one
on the mark, okay?
You can do it.
And camera! And sound!
Scene 17, take three.
Mark.
Action.
Well, hello, college.
Cut! No good for sound.
Well, fucking hell, Lloyd.
Could you just let us
get through one take?
Why would I do that
if you won't be able to use it?
You told me to do it quiet.
That's why I did it quiet.
Quiet, not inarticulate.
You can't mumble.
This is bullshit.
Are we going again or what?
I can't breathe in here!
We're going again!
And camera and sound!
Scene 17, take four.
Mark.
Action.
Well, hello, college!
Motherfucker!
Who opened the door?
All right, everybody,
eyes on me!
Any other faggots
who ignore that red light...
You're alternating
the pitch of your voice
too much.
Okay, can you just--
Lloyd, Lloyd, fuck off.
Fuck off.
I listen to my fucking director,
not the fucking sound guy!
Who the fu--
Mr. Wallach, so happy
you're joining us. Come on.
Maybe try staying
more monotone.
Okay.
And camera and sound!
Yeah, okay.
Scene 17, take five.
Mark.
Action.
Well, hello, college.
Hiya, this is Joanne
from Gray--
Cut!
Motherfucking shit!
Cocksucking-- What the fuck?
What the fuck happened now?
I'm hearing
a high-pitched noise.
Yeah, it's her voice.
- Do you hear that?
- For fuck's sake.
Do you hear? That squeak?
Is anybody wearing a watch?
No.
I'm telling you,
I can't stay in there
that long.
It's a fucking hotbox!
I get it, Bill.
Nobody is comfortable
in here.
Quiet!
What is that fucking sound?
We gotta move this along.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Wallach.
We'll get this under control,
I promise you.
"Hiya, this is Joanne
from 31 Grimes Hall."
Fuck! Grays Hall.
"I just wanted to see--
Who is this?"
Hey, Count? Count?
I need a red one.
Yeah, yeah.
"The" Count.
It's just The Count.
Just next time
say, "The Count."
Now's not really
"The" fucking time.
Found it!
It's a pin in Ruth's ankle.
Did you have surgery?
If you can just
keep your right leg
absolutely still.
And camera and sound!
Scene 17, take six.
Mark.
Action.
Well, hello, college.
Who sneezed?
Who the fuck sneezed?
Kike-nosed, Hymie-hole
piece of mongoloid shit!
I see you.
Oh, I see you right there,
you little Shylock dickface.
Wipe your nose again!
Wipe your little hook nose,
you menorah motherfucker!
Now, does anyone else here
need to sneeze? Huh?
Does anyone else here need
to fuck this scene in the ass?
Camera! And sound!
Scene 17, take seven.
Mark.
Action.
Hello, college.
Nell, your mark!
Fuck this shit!
Fuck. Lloyd.
It's a million
fucking degrees!
We gotta move the mic.
Or you could fucking direct her
to hit her fucking mark.
But why is it so fucking hard?
You're right!
I didn't realize
we were making Ben-Hur!
I can move it right now.
My whole year is wide open.
We could shoot this thing
through fucking New Year's.
Wherever the fuck those
little feet of hers want to go,
I can move the mic for them!
Okay, calm down!
Get off of me! I dare you!
I fucking dare you!
Get off the set!
You're good.
Un-fucking-professional!
Okay. Okay, Lloyd,
ready to go again?
You want me to use this chalk?
Make the mark bigger for you?
Okay, we're gonna go again.
It's fine. No, it's fine.
The mark's right here.
I'm gonna kick
your fucking ass!
Oh, yeah! Come on! Come on!
Can we go?
I'm gonna have a fucking
heart attack in here.
Get back
in your fucking box, Bill!
I can't even believe this.
Everyone, shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
That's not how we make movies.
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
Now, if anyone
stops this scene again,
I will shit on you!
I will shit in your mouth,
I promise you!
Is that clear, Lloyd?
Is that good for fucking sound?
Now, we are going again!
Camera!
And motherfucking sound!
- Scene 17, take eight.
- Mark.
Action.
Hello, college.
Hello?
Hiya, this is Joanne
from 31 Grays Hall.
I was just gonna see
if the phone worked.
Who is this?
You don't say. The Dean!
Well, how you doin'?
It's a nice campus
you got here.
So, uh,
what's a girl supposed to do
once she's here?
Sure, classes.
But ain't you got
any parties?
Not till the evening, huh?
All right,
I can handle that.
I'm from Granville, Ohio,
so I know quiet.
Thanks a bunch, Dean.
See you later.
Nice fella.
Wonder if he's single.
Cut! Cut!
We did it!
Yes, we did it!
- Okay, check the gate!
- Billy, check the gate!
Billy!
Bill!
Billy, come on.
Bill-- Let's get a crowbar.
Come on. Hurry up.
Bill!
Oh, my God.
He's dead.
Manuel!
Meet Estelle.
She's from Broadway.
She's a real actor.
We got engaged yesterday.
Now she's trying to explain
to me that movies are a low art.
Mucho gusto. Drinks?
Double shot of tequila.
Water, darling.
Hola, Jacky!
Hola, Carmelita.
I have no idea who that is.
The point is, darling,
I believe movies are
every bit as profound.
And with sync sound,
which, who knows,
could be what
the discovery of perspective
was for painting,
I think what we have here
in Hollywood is high art.
It's--
Party time, sparkle cocks!
Hot damn!
Jack Conrad?
Hmm.
You are even more fuckable
in person.
Thank you.
This is Estelle.
His fiancée.
Fiancée?
Hey, I'm not actually
gonna fuck him.
I beat the whole
USC football team at a game
of craps when we wrapped,
so now they have to be
my slaves for the night.
Jack, can you say hi
to my dad, please?
Sure.
He wanted to meet you.
He's also my manager.
It's a good thing we met, Jack.
I got a business proposition
just for you.
A Nellie-themed diner.
I'm gonna call it
"The Wild Child Grill."
I'm gonna serve sandwiches
shaped like her face.
It's not a threat,
it's just what it is.
If you keep playing flat,
I'm gonna fucking headbutt you,
and it's just gonna be
what it's gonna be.
You need to play better.
You embarrassing us.
Joe, you hear what
he just said to me?
Listen to this psychopath.
When you gonna do something?
Why you worried about Joe?
Nigga, when are you
gonna do something?
Have you ever heard
of Alexander Scriabin?
Why the fuck do I care
about Alexander Scriabin?
Alexander Scriabin
was a Russian pianist.
Broke his hands
just so his fingers could
stretch across the keys better.
I'm saying if I fucking
headbutt you across them
funky-ass lips of yours,
you might start playing
a little better.
We can hope.
You're fucking deranged,
Sidney.
Elinor's trying to
civilize me for talkies.
Ain't that nice?
"Isn't that nice?"
Isn't.
And more attire next time.
A little more attire's
always in the way.
Nellie dresses low
'cause Nellie is low.
Now, let me tell you
about the time I fought
a rattlesnake.
It was Death Valley.
April.
Jack? It's George.
Aw, Georgie.
Who was it this time?
Claire.
Well, Claire's a lesbian.
That's an uphill battle
for anyone.
Come on, buddy,
get your head out of there.
Let's go get a drink.
Okay, okay, I'll stop.
I'm stuck.
What?
Get me the fuck out of here!
Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention, please!
For your entertainment
this evening,
Miss Lady Fay Zhu
will now choose a partner.
Hi.
I'm Nellie LaRoy's dad.
What's your name?
Cannonball!
You're great, man.
You call my office
'cause we're gonna
need more musicians.
And you're talented,
man.
Mr. Thalberg,
it's an honor to meet--
Yeah, I'm gonna
go throw up now.
Spoke to my friend at Kinoscope.
He said the movie's a disaster.
- LaRoy's?
- Yeah.
They went double the budget
'cause she could never hit
her fucking mark
and her voice sounds
like a dying pig.
No, seriously, apparently
the footage is so awful,
Wallach's already thinking
about dumping her.
I'm not surprised.
She never had any talent anyway.
Oh, my God. Zero.
Filthy, slutty piece
of fucking trash
with a nasty voice.
You meet her dad?
Oh, my God.
He's even more embarrassing
than she is. Fucking idiot.
Goodbye!
Don't come back!
It's the end, I'm telling you.
It's the end for all of 'em.
All the frogs.
Don't be a fucking baby.
And that, that
is when I grabbed the snake
by the head.
The big fucking man!
There he is!
What?
What's he telling you?
What was he saying to you?
The snake story.
Come on, buddy.
You got it, yeah.
Dad, I have an idea.
Why don't you fight a snake--
a real one-- right now?
Come on.
Okay, no problemo.
Let's go fight a snake.
Okay!
Fucking listen up,
all you big-dick Mister Men!
Who wants to see my dad
fight a fucking snake?
Fuck yeah!
A snake's getting fought!
Yeah, I mean,
Chaplin is hung for sure,
but Gary Cooper--
Gary Cooper is a fucking horse!
He's also a fucking pussy.
All that cock...
...no balls.
A shame.
What are the schlongs
like on Broadway?
You want some?
No, thank you.
Doesn't look that bad, buddy.
Stop!
Sweetie, come on.
Please don't...
Thank you.
Please, hurry!
This can't be where we--
Where are we?
Where'd he go?
Holy fuck!
Out of my way!
Huh. Huh.
No! Stand--
Stand-- Stand back.
Back!
I'm gonna fight a snake.
Whoo!
Look, sweetie,
he's gonna fight a snake.
Isn't this great?
Here we go.
Ha!
See that snake?
See this man?
Watch this.
So, first,
one must assume
the position of a mongoose!
I'm not-- I'm just gonna--
Tell me that--
If I could just've
done the whole thing
over and over and over!
If I could just
fucking defend--
Yeah-- Fighting...
If I could just...
I--
Aw!
Motherfucker!
Who is gonna fight it?
No, I'm not onboard.
I'm scared.
I got practice.
I'm allergic.
Goddamn it,
you fucking pussies!
You fucking piece-of-shit,
fucking bullshit,
fucking pussies!
The night is almost over.
I got a 10:00 a.m. call time.
I just want to see
a motherfucking snake fight!
Nellie, babe--
Don't "Nellie, babe" me,
you six-foot vagina!
I will fight it!
- No, no, no!
- Yes!
I'm more man
than any of you.
Nellie, Nellie.
I ain't a fucking pussy!
Nellie...
Oh!
See? You see that?
It's that fucking easy!
You chickenshit--
Nellie!
It's not letting go!
Nellie! Nellie!
Let it go. Let it--
Hey! Hey, I got it!
Help me! Help me!
Jack!
Jack, do something!
Right. Once more
into the breach, dear friends!
Once more!
Jacky!
Help us!
For fuck's sake.
Welcome to the wonderful
world of sound!
I have to do this?
What do you mean?
It's gonna be great!
Just stand there and sing?
Exactly.
While it's raining.
Yeah.
And that's Noah's Ark?
Uh, I believe so, yeah.
Because
it's raining so much?
To be honest with you,
I don't really know
why it's Noah's Ark.
Georgie.
Come on, come on.
No. No.
What? This is--
Norma's here.
Buster Keaton's here.
George, no. No.
The song's a hit.
You love to sing.
Oh, I hate you.
I hate you.
Come on.
Just don't
let Olga shoot me.
Okay.
Cut! Cut!
Musicians, you're on a break.
I wanna work with my actors
for a second.
The head bobbing,
it's very mechanical right now.
Think of something
that makes it personal
to you. Okay?
That's a little too much, Mary.
That's too personal. Okay?
So just bobbing, all right?
Let's work on that.
Up. Up. Rest of the body
doesn't move.
Up. Up. Up. Up. Up. Up.
Very good, Mary.
Oh, I like this.
Isolate the shoulders.
What do you think?
Up. Up. Up.
You're asking me
what I think?
Okay.
Yeah.
This looks
so much better.
I think you got
those cameras pointed
in the wrong direction.
Do the rainbow, remember?
Big arms!
That's what I think.
Take this one more time.
Everybody ready?
Musicians are ready?
And action!
Up. Up. Up. Up. Up. Up.
Up. Up.
Bob. Bob. Bob.
Bob. Bob. That's better.
Good. Good, good, Candace.
Very good.
Yeah, it's coming together.
This is much better.
Remember that energy.
Cut!
Good idea.
Manuel Torres.
How have you been?
Uh, well, sir. And you?
Y-You want to talk
with Mr. Thalberg?
Were these Sid Palmer shorts
your idea?
They're more
like a collaboration
between Sidney and me.
Uh-huh.
How'd you like to leave MGM,
come be sound chief
at Kinoscope?
What?
We need
Spanish-language pictures.
We're taking new directions.
It's changing times, Manny.
I'm honored, sir, but...
And we need to do something
about Nellie LaRoy.
Oh, yeah.
You know her, don't you?
The Jersey thing
doesn't work anymore.
Today's audiences
find her pornographic.
She's been hanging around
Jim McKay's casinos
like a half-wit.
She owes gambling debts
all over town.
And she sounds
like a donkey.
I mean...
Anyways...
think about it.
Gentlemen, here's the plan.
We turn Nellie LaRoy
into a lady.
We change her parts.
We fix her voice.
No more drugs.
No more gambling.
Elinor St. John
writes a story about
her amazing transformation.
With the right endorsements,
and with Elinor as an ally,
we can remake Miss LaRoy
into an actress
of sophistication.
Like the ladies of MGM.
Next, Sidney Palmer.
Today's white audiences
want Negroes
in their pictures.
Negro music,
Negro voices.
So we bring Sidney to Kinoscope,
whatever he costs.
One moment, gentlemen.
One moment.
Um, Sidney Palmer, okay?
Sidney Palmer.
I was hoping I could introduce
the two of you.
Miss LaRoy, meet Mr. Torres.
Mr. Torres,
meet Miss LaRoy.
Mr. Torres is gonna be
working for us
here at Kinoscope.
Hi, Mr. Torres.
Just want you to know
that I'm ready to change,
and I'll do
whatever you need.
Call me Manny.
Cut!
Beautiful.
Bellísimo, bellísimo.
Next time, try softer, okay?
"But why, my darling Pierre?
Why?"
Walt! Walt, hey!
Move that microphone
45 degrees, okay?
That one near her,
okay?
- Amigo, no, no, no.
- Hey... ... amigo!
It's not "Manuel,"
it's "Manny."
Manny Torres.
- Not Manuel, okay?
- Phone for you, sir!
Yeah.
- Manny Torres.
- Manuel.
Moving up fast.
Jack? I'm sorry.
I meant to call you.
The reds chill her out.
Blues keep her skinny.
Don't say a word.
I'm happy for you.
You deserve this.
Did you see my screen test yet, Manny?
Now go show
those fat fucks
how it's done.
Okay! Okay!
Let's roll, people!
Let's go! Take two!
"Pierre, who is the fella
to whom you are speaking?"
"Who is the fellow..."
Fellow.
Fellow. Fuck.
Welcome to your new home,
Mr. Palmer.
And your car.
A gift from
Mr. Wallach.
And that finishes at 5:30,
leaving you enough time
to make the gala.
And a Hearst invite
has come in
for Miss LaRoy.
Only question is,
what do we do about Fay Zhu?
It won't help Nellie
with the Hearst crowd.
"Listen to me, Catherine.
I don't care if they find us.
They could strip me of my rank
and it wouldn't change
how I feel."
Latest voice tests:
Conrad Nagel, rich tone.
William Haines,
good consonants.
You're messing
with Nellie's career,
and we're trying so hard
to get it back on track.
There's a new
sensibility now.
People care about morals.
"I've known loss.
I've known pain.
You're what gives me life."
Try accenting "you"
a little more,
darling.
"You are what gives me life."
Just a suggestion.
Marion Davies stutters a bit.
Maybe supporting roles
from now on?
This sort of thing
is no longer acceptable.
"You are what gives me life."
Maybe try it slower.
Ramon Novarro can play guitar,
but south-of-the-border accent.
What I'm trying to say
is Kinoscope can no longer
employ you.
Your image is not helpful,
and we don't
need titles anymore.
That's it.
I'm sorry.
Jack Conrad has a good voice,
is our biggest asset.
Also the most expensive.
- Yeah?
- "You are what gives me life.
I love you."
Then what I'd suggest there
would be to--
Hello?
Jack, it's Irv.
Listen, there's no good way
to say this--
They found George in his home
this morning.
Looks like he struck out
with a girl he was seeing.
He shot himself.
Jack?
Thank you.
So, what I would suggest there
would be to play subtext
rather than--
Honey?
Are you okay?
He was the first one
to say I have talent.
He saved my life.
Who?
It's not a low art, you know.
I want you to know that.
What I do means something
to millions of people.
My folks didn't have the money
or the education
to go to the theater,
so they went
to the vaudeville houses,
and then the nickelodeons.
And you know what?
There's beauty there.
What happens up on that screen
means something.
Maybe not to you
in your ivory tower.
But for real people
on the ground,
it means something.
Jack, I-I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Of course you don't.
Of course you don't!
A hundred thousand people
see you on Broadway,
and it's the smash
of the century, right?
Well, here it's a flop!
A fucking flop!
So do me a favor, darling.
Save your subtext
recommendations
for your pretentious
Eugene O'Neill-Henrik Ibsen
jerk-offs
that only a handful
of rich geriatrics
give two fucks about,
and I'll do what I do
without your help!
Huh?
Listen, Catherine.
I don't care if they find us.
They could strip me of my rank
and it wouldn't change
how I feel.
I've known loss.
I've known pain.
It's you who gives me life.
I love you.
You think it works?
It's great.
It's a winner, Jack.
You think it works?
I wish George
could've seen it.
Yes.
Mr. Conrad,
you're gonna miss your train.
Christ!
Ah, fuck.
I'm off to repair my marriage.
I'll see you bastards
in a month.
Good luck with that.
Okay, don't forget.
Your friend Manuel
pulled a lot of strings
to get you in here.
These people choose
who stays and who goes.
So show them that you're
a lady of sophistication
and you'll be
back on top.
So, now what
did we discuss?
"-ing" not "-in."
"Isn't" not "ain't."
Mm-hmm.
And when in doubt,
say somethin' French.
Perfection!
Also, no drinking,
and try not to eat too much.
Billy! Marion!
Oh, Elinor!
Hello.
May I please present to you
Miss Nellie LaRoy.
How do you do?
Enchantée.
Good evening,
Miss LaRoy.
Oh.
Nell, I'd like you
to also meet Mildred Yates.
Sir Delmer Lunny.
And Jonathan
and Harriet Rothschild.
Pleasure.
Gerald,
have you heard about
the new Ellis Engel picture?
It sounds just awful.
Yes, I've spoken
to L.B. about it already.
There'll be no more
of that kind of thing,
I can assure you.
Here we have a pâté de campagne
designed by Krümt
with a Takagei bubble.
I hear it's Strindberg season
in New York.
Do you like Miss Julie?
Yes, she is lovely
and very talented.
Sidney.
Manny.
All right.
Billy, is your new rug
really a Klikó?
I got it last spring.
One of a kind.
Mr. Palmer.
It is truly an honor
to meet you.
Teddy and I
saw Cottage Blues last week.
Genius!
Thanks.
Do you play bridge,
Miss LaRoy?
You're from Mexico, then?
Uh, Spain. Madrid.
Spain. Madrid.
Wow.
How did you get into music,
Mr. Palmer?
Uh, I taught myself, mostly.
Incredible.
Who are your influences?
Uh, Scriabin.
Ah.
I like Rachmaninoff.
Do you think George Eliot
was better as a novelist
or a poet, Nell?
I think he was marvelous,
marvelous at both.
Now I do apologize,
but I must resign briefly
to the powder room.
I shan't be long. Ta-ta!
...everything you need,
you know, right here.
It's got the restaurants and--
Of course,
now you can't gamble in LA.
You been to Cal-Neva?
This one guy McKay
owns a few joints,
but he's a little scary, so--
One moment, please.
Oh, sure.
Jack! Didn't think
you'd get in in time.
How was Europe?
Inspiring! Di--
And congrats
on the new film.
Opens tonight,
right?
Correct.
Did you know
Michelangelo painted
the entire Sistine Chapel
on his back?
Manny! How's our girl doing?
Oh, She's doing great.
Perfect.
Okay, good.
Manny, I need to go home.
You cannot go home.
I can't do this.
You're going back out there.
I'm having a heart attack.
Elinor and I worked so hard
to get you into this.
Manny,
I am dying out there.
Okay, okay.
They're a bunch of--
They're awful.
Mildred's got a fucking rabbit
on her shoulders
that's probably still alive.
Hey.
The ass-pincher!
They can save your career.
They don't like me!
If they like you...
They don't!
...we get the right director,
the right publicity--
What about Ruth?
I need Ruth back.
Ruth doesn't fucking cut it
anymore!
Listen to me,
I'm here for you.
It's you and me.
You could be a star again,
Nellie. Again.
It's you and me.
You look beautiful,
okay?
I look fucking ridiculous.
What's your name?
Nellie LaRoy.
Perfect. Once again.
In French.
It is French already!
Okay, let's go.
"Roy" means "king," remember?
Beautiful.
Jack.
It's great to see you.
You, too. Salud.
Are you holding up?
Well, I do miss him.
Uh...
Miss him?
George.
What were you
referring to?
Uh...
Jack.
How was Europe?
Great!
And good to be home.
That's the attitude.
Staying strong.
Where have you been?
She's fine.
And what do you think
of the new wave
of race films, Mr. Palmer?
I find the studios' committees
for the casting of Negroes
inspiring, don't you?
And he replies,
"Do they need an electrician?"
Do you know any good jokes,
Nellie?
Yeah, I--
Nell prefers listening to jokes
rather than telling them.
Come on, tell us a joke.
I have a joke.
Harold Lloyd and I
were in France...
Hey, how you holding up?
You, too?
Well, I guess the movie
isn't a hit.
So be it.
I'm sure you'll get
another chance.
Why wouldn't I
get another chance?
No, it just--
What I mean--
Would someone kindly tell me
what the fuck is going on?
He shows up with a mime.
I go,
"Harold, my croque monsieur is
worth a lot more than a mime!"
Nell, you must have
some good ones.
Well, I-I--
I am not the best joke teller.
Come on, Nellie.
Isn't being funny what you do?
Yeah, I believe
that films like yours
are gentle
but virile olive branches
in these divided times.
That is my cue.
I should be going.
Please, you must play for us.
Come on, Nellie.
We'll approve your next picture.
- Yes, Nellie, be funny.
- You know, I just thought of one.
Two fish
are on their honeymoon--
Actually, I got one.
A bear and a rabbit are
shittin' in the woods one day.
And the bear
says to the rabbit,
"Hey, do ya ever have a problem
with the shit
stickin' to your fur?"
And the rabbit finishes shittin'
and he says,
"No, I never do. Why?"
And the bear says,
"Fan-fuckin'-tastic!"
And he grabs the rabbit
behind the ears
and...
I can't believe
you just...
Why not?
Why? Haven't you heard
what they say about me?
I'm a degenerate
fucking animal.
"Oh, Nellie!" Look at them.
"Who knows what she might do?
She's from Jersey, you know."
This is what
a degenerate fucking animal
from Jersey does.
That's what
the degenerate fuckin' animal
from Jersey does.
So you know what?
I'm gonna let you all go on
fucking your cousins,
polishing your guest lists,
plying your underaged
fuckin' mistresses
with fuckin' Beaujolais,
you sick fucks!
I'm the animal?
What is this shit?
I'm the sick one!
I'm the fuckin' crazy one!
You people make me fucking sick!
You're not better than me!
You're not!
You're not fucking better
than me.
I don't need this shit.
You know what?
I'm gonna go home, I'm gonna
stick some coke up my pussy,
and you all can stick
your champagne flutes
up your rose-smellin',
candy-tastin',
snow-white fuckin' assholes!
My rug!
You puked on my rug!
Please, before it's too late.
You can't stay here.
They'll find you.
They'll find us.
Listen, Catherine.
I don't care if they find us.
They could strip me of my rank
and it wouldn't change
how I feel.
I've known loss.
I've known pain.
It's you who gives me life.
Catherine...
I love you.
I love you, I love you,
"I love you, I love you!"
"I love you!"
Jack Conrad.
What are your thoughts
for the future?
Well, my last two movies
didn't work,
but I learned a lot from 'em.
There were things
I'd taken for granted...
that maybe I shouldn't have.
Well, you're still
MGM's biggest asset.
You still command
the biggest paycheck.
And I'd like to earn it.
I'm still learning
this new language.
Is it true
that you've quit drinking?
Yeah.
It was getting in the way.
I'm not gonna let
that happen anymore.
There's a lot of acting talent
coming in from the theater now.
Might you go to the stage
to gain more experience?
Elinor, I will master
the talking film on film.
Do you miss
the silents?
No.
We shouldn't stand
in the way of progress.
Okay.
Thanks, Jack.
You're still the kid
I met 20 years ago,
you know.
You haven't changed...
...a bit.
Thank you, Elinor.
Neither have you.
We're ready for you on set,
Mr. Palmer.
She's not gonna
fuck this up again, is she?
I guarantee you,
she's going to blow you away.
- Is she ready? Hurry.
- I'll check.
You good with the money?
Looks realistic.
Yeah. What about the gun?
We're still having a problem
with the firing mechanism.
¡No, carajo!
It still sounds like that?
Hi there.
It's Jack calling for Irving.
Jack Conrad.
One o'clock. All right, fine.
I'll call back then. Thanks.
There you are.
We have a serious
fucking problem.
What?
The band looks mixed.
What do you mean?
I mean, the other players
are a lot darker than Sid.
So?
Manny, do you think
I could say a line?
No! Get back to the shot!
In your wide, next to them,
Sidney looks white.
But he's Black.
They won't think that
in the South.
To them, this'll look
like a mixed band. We won't
be able to book the movie there.
The South is big money.
That's half the revenue lost.
No, that's not possible.
Nellie needs this movie to work.
Forget working,
it's not even worth
finishing at that rate.
Wallach'll just
pull the plug.
What do you suggest?
Oh, he did, did he?
Okay, then I'll call back
at 4:00. Thanks.
Sidney?
Yeah.
Why?
For the lighting.
Just to match
the other players.
For the lighting.
Sí.
I know.
But look around.
Your fellow players,
if we don't get the shot,
the studio will shut
the picture down
and they won't get paid.
You're an actor now,
Sidney.
Actors change
their appearance
for roles.
It's normal.
It's going to be on you,
Sidney.
You are risking
all these guys' ability to
feed their families over makeup.
Gracias.
We all good?
Left for the day. Huh.
Well, here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna come down there
and see for myself.
No, that's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
Thank you.
I'm sorry,
I just can't have you in here
right now.
He left for the day,
but I can take a message
for you--
Thank you.
Cut!
That is a wrap on Sid.
Uh, Mr. Torres?
We can't find Miss LaRoy.
Yeah?
She's gone.
Going over to Stage 4!
You'll need that
to come back.
It's okay. I won't be back.
Madame? Let's chat.
I'm on a deadline,
darling.
You know,
when I first moved to LA,
you know what the signs
on all the doors read?
"No actors or dogs allowed."
Yeah, I changed that.
I helped build this place
you call home.
I've never had any illusions
about us. I've never pretended
we're friends.
We're friendly.
I scratch yours,
you scratch mine.
That's our work.
But this?
This is something else.
What do you want, Jack?
I want to know
why you wrote it.
No, you want to know
why they laughed.
Would you like me to tell you?
Why they laughed.
Sure, Elinor. Why?
There is no why.
It wasn't your voice.
It wasn't a conspiracy.
And it certainly
wasn't anything I wrote.
There's nothing
you could have done differently.
There's nothing you can do.
Your time has run out.
There is no why.
Stop questioning it.
I'm on a dry spell.
No.
It's over.
It's been over for a while.
I'm sorry.
Elinor, you peddle gossip.
You don't make anything.
You don't know what it is
to put yourself out there.
You're just a cockroach.
I've been counted out before.
This isn't new to me.
Have you ever stopped
to think why,
when there's a house fire,
the people die
and the cockroaches all survive?
Jesus Christ.
What happened was you thought
the house needed you.
It doesn't.
Doesn't need you any more
than it needs the roaches.
And the roaches,
knowing this,
crawl back into the dark,
lay low, and make it through.
See, but you,
you held the spotlight.
It's those of us in the dark,
the ones who just watch,
who survive.
A house fire.
And there'll be
hundreds more like it, too.
An earthquake could
wipe this town off the map
and wouldn't make a difference.
It's the idea that sticks.
There'll be a hundred more
Jack Conrads.
Hundred more me's.
Hundred more conversations
just like this one,
over and over again,
until God knows when.
Because it's bigger than you.
I know it hurts.
No one asks
to be left behind.
But in a hundred years,
when you and I
are both long gone,
any time someone
threads a frame of yours
through a sprocket,
you will be alive again.
You see what that means?
One day, every person
on every film
shot this year will be dead.
And one day, all those films
will be pulled from the vaults,
and all their ghosts
will dine together,
and adventure together,
go to the jungle,
to war together.
A child born in 50 years
will stumble across your image
flickering on a screen
and feel he knows you,
like-- like a friend,
though you breathed your last
before he breathed his first.
You've been given a gift.
Be grateful.
Your time today is through,
but you'll spend eternity
with angels and ghosts.
Thank you for that.
Manny!
I need your help.
I'm in so much trouble
and I really need your help.
Calm down
and tell me what happened.
I fucked up, Manny.
And I know you've
been trying to help me,
and I've kept fucking up.
Now I really need your help,
and I hate to ask--
Calm down.
Cálmate.
Okay, yeah,
I was in Cal-Neva,
and I was playing cards
and there was--
This guy, McKay,
runs the place and, he's--
like, you don't fuck with--
How much?
He's...
It's a lot. It's a lot.
How much do you owe?
Eighty-five grand.
They took me...
¿Como? How?
He took me back into a room,
Manny, and they said
if I don't have the money
by the end of the week,
they're gonna pour acid
on my pussy.
And they're not kidding.
They will fucking kill you.
These people are killers.
Pay them, okay?
I can't.
You don't fuck
with these kind of people.
You just pay them.
I can't pay them.
What do you mean?
I don't have the money
to pay them. I don't have--
You're Nellie LaRoy.
Of course you have the money.
No, I don't. It's--
It's gone.
My dad's diner and the--
We don't own the house.
I don't have that--
I don't have that money.
...fucking help!
Please be nice to me, Manny.
Please.
You fucked my life!
I have nowhere else to go.
You're my only friend.
You're the only one, Manny!
You're the only one
who's ever been nice to me.
who's ever cared.
I've always helped you,
and all you've done
is break my heart!
Please.
They're gonna kill me.
I tried.
Manny,
I did everything you said.
I tried.
Don't go home.
Stay here
for a couple of days.
I'm gonna fix it.
Thank you.
I'll fix it.
Jack! It's Irv.
Jack?
Listen, I've been trying you
for a while.
I got some great news.
I got a job for you.
Prestige one.
Lead got sick mid-shoot.
Quick start, quick wrap.
Need you, Jack.
Jack?
Yeah.
Hear what I said?
Yeah, I heard.
Okay? So?
What do you think?
Yeah. I just have
one question.
It's a piece of shit,
isn't it?
What?
And I'd be
bailing you out,
wouldn't I?
No. No. Of course not.
Irv, let's just call it
for what it is.
That's all I ask.
I'll do your movie.
I'll bail you out.
All I want in return
is a little honesty.
Can you do that, Irv?
Can you be honest with me
for ten seconds or so?
I'd be bailing you out,
wouldn't I?
Yeah,
you'd be bailing me out.
And it's
a piece of shit,
isn't it?
Yeah,
it's a piece of shit.
Okay, Irv.
I'll see you on set.
Mr. Conrad?
Harold, how you doing?
I'm doing good, Jack.
How about you?
I'm doing okay.
How many movies
have we done together now?
This makes 82.
Huh.
Eighty-two.
That's right.
Beautiful, isn't she?
The great wide ocean.
You remember
your first time at sea?
Kid, I'll never forget it.
Cut! Fantastic!
Not a dry eye in the house.
Great. For this next take...
Yeah.
...I want to see more of
that real emotion.
Okay.
You know?
Really dig into it.
Yeah.
Find it out here.
Find it on that horizon.
Yeah.
A never-ending horizon
that has brought you
all the way to this point.
Brought you so far in life.
You know?
Jack?
You good to go again?
Sure.
Nellie?
Manny!
Manny, I got it all figured out.
Because I know that
you've been trying to
get my career going.
I've had an idea.
I was thinking I can dance.
If I can dance,
I bet I can sing.
'Cause you can do anything
if you set your mind to it.
Nellie, you have to
stop this, okay?
You really have to stop.
I'm figuring out
how to get the money.
Exactly! This is how
we make the money back.
I'm gonna tell Wallach
that we're gonna
finish the movie, okay?
And first, all this,
all this fucking mess
that you are doing
every fucking day
is part of your process.
Manny, it's gonna be like
nothing anyone's ever seen.
Hello?
Manny, it's done.
I got the money
and I know a guy
who will set the meet.
You got it?
Okay, but-- but you're going to
be there, right?
Don't worry,
I'll be there the whole time.
See you Friday.
Nellie, we did it, okay?
Fuck Don Wallach!
Fuck all of this shit, okay?
Fuck him, Manny! Yes!
Fuck it! Fuck it!
How did you
get the money so fast?
I have my ways. Don't worry.
And it's all in here?
Yes.
How do you know the guy?
I sold him keys
a while back.
He works for McKay.
So, we give him the bag,
he calls McKay, and the threat
against Nellie is off.
Okay, okay.
I'm not used to
this kind of people.
They're no worse
than movie people.
You good?
Yeah, yeah. Let's go.
Remember. A monologue
in the next picture.
Wilson.
Been a while.
Good to see you.
Meet Manny.
Nice to meet you, Manny.
And nice to meet you, sir.
I believe this belongs to you.
You're a producer?
Um, a studio executive.
Jim heard
you were a big producer.
He's here now.
He'd love to
buy you guys a drink.
That's very kind of him,
but--
Sounds great. Yeah.
Great. Follow me.
Gotta be polite.
One drink.
Fuck.
Jim.
This is Manny
and The Count.
How do you boys do?
I'm James McKay.
How do you do, sir?
Hello.
Sit down.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Do you want a drink?
It's brandy mixed with ether.
Yes.
Sure.
Wilson, will you
get us some drinks, please?
Sir, I-- I just wanted to say
how sorry I am
that things got out of hand.
Nonsense.
You came through.
That's what counts.
So, you boys are friends
with Nellie LaRoy?
Um, yeah.
Mmm.
Too bad what happened
to her career, huh?
Such a shame, yeah.
It's sad.
Her new movie will work.
So you're the movie producer.
Uh, studio executive.
I got some movie ideas myself.
You wanna hear them?
Yes.
Please.
Okay.
Mmm.
Okay, so,
there's a 10-year-old kid
and he's a prodigy
at all these adult things.
He's supersmart with words.
He can play the piano
and recite Lincoln
and all this stuff.
Here's the twist:
Turns out
he's a 50-year-old midget.
He only looks like he's a kid.
The joke's on us.
That's really good. Wow.
It's very good.
It's great, yeah.
Very good.
I am sorry.
I'm gonna check on the drinks.
I don't know where Wilson went.
Stupid...
One drink and we leave.
Right after this we leave.
Calm down.
I am calm, cabrón.
No, you're not.
You're very nervous.
I'm not here for drinks
and fun, okay?
I'm in your debt.
You're not in my debt.
Whose money it is?
The guy makes it
by the kilo.
It's not a big deal.
What guy?
You never told me
how you got it.
Tony. The prop guy.
I thought I told you that.
It's the prop guy's money?
No, it's the money
that he makes.
What do you mean?
Like, uh, his income?
No, it's his--
It's from your
bank heist picture.
It's movie money.
It's prop money.
The money in the bag
is prop money?
Well, where was I
gonna get 85 grand
in two days?
We have to go now,
pendejo cabrón!
Calm.
Um, have I, uh,
interrupted something?
No, no.
Oh, thank you.
I got more ideas.
You ever heard of Wyatt Earp?
He died a couple of years ago.
I met him once.
Little known fact:
The greatest hero
of the Wild West
couldn't count.
No?
No.
So I was thinking,
you make a movie about him,
and in it,
you make him
full-fledged retard.
What?
You okay?
You're sweating.
It's probably the ether.
It's--
Oh.
I thought you were just
excited about the idea.
My next idea's my best:
The world's most
fearless warrior.
I know just the guy to play him.
You just build the movie
around him.
He is sensational.
He is?
Would you like to meet him?
Sure. Um, I--
I can have the studio set--
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm going to see him now.
He's at the Blockhouse.
Where is that?
It's just over the hill.
A few minutes' drive.
Wilson and I can
take you there and back.
It's the best party in town.
Mmm.
It's, uh-- It's very late
and we have to go.
Oh, no, no, it's worth it.
I promise you.
I mean, I appreciate it,
but we have to go.
Trust me.
You'll never forget it.
Um, what's this?
It's LA's last real party.
Wilson, bring that cash.
This town
has gotten so repressed.
This is the only place left
where you can have
any fun these days.
Welcome to the asshole
of Los Angeles.
He's two floors down!
Follow me!
This city used to know
how to have a good time.
It's such a drag now.
They still know
how to party here, though.
♪ There's one pet I like to pet
And every evening we get set ♪
♪ I stroke it every chance I get
It's my girl's pussy... ♪
♪ Seldom plays
And never purrs... ♪
One more floor.
♪ But I don't mind
Because it's hers ♪
♪ My girl's pussy ♪
This is
the kind of thing
your industry needs.
Hollywood has just
become so stale.
Don't you agree?
Not this floor, either.
- Wilson, isn't he on tonight?
- Thought he was.
Sir?
It-- It's very late.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I promised you a sight.
You're getting a sight.
Let's try one more floor.
Bear with me, fellas.
Wait till you see this guy.
I think we can
make millions together!
Oh, shit!
That was so good!
Oh, come on, boys,
it's just on the other side.
It's worth it, I promise.
Okay.
Oh, yes. This is it.
Yeah.
Yes. I think I can hear him.
Come on.
Oh...
Yes.
I'm so excited for you.
You're gonna love him!
Yes! Yes!
He's the next big thing!
Whoo!
Incredible, isn't he?
You either are a star
or you aren't.
And he is!
Watch what he does.
It has to be seen
to be believed.
Keep watching.
Yes! Whoo!
He's just made
for the movies, isn't he?
They found him
in a forest in Oregon.
He will do anything
for cash.
Wilson, quick,
give me a 20.
More! Eat another rat!
Give me another one.
It's fake.
No.
No, come on.
Let-- Let me explain--
We were gonna
make movies together.
Let-Let-Let me explain.
Please.
No, no, no, no, no!
Hey, no, no, no, no!
What the fuck?
Back off! Back off!
Oh, shit! Go! God!
You have to see Dresden.
It's the most beautiful city in Germany.
- Jack said he was gonna take me to Greece.
-  Greece?
Isn't that right, honey?
That's right.
The architecture is amazing.
You'll love it.
- Santoríni.
- I hear it's so beautiful.
Fay!
Jack.
Folks, I'd like to introduce you
to the wild and wonderful
Lady Fay.
This is Rebecca.
This is Lewis.
- How do you do?
- Hello.
- What's your excuse?
Just wandering through?
Mmm. Something like that.
Let me get you a drink.
Were you shooting?
No.
Just wanted some air.
What's next?
I'm going to Europe,
actually.
Are you?
Yeah, Pathé wants me.
That's great!
Pathé's got really good taste.
Thank you.
Jack's back!
Way to go, Jack!
So how's your movie?
It's shit.
Another giant swing
at mediocrity.
Well, the girl seems nice.
She is.
And she has no idea
it'll end like all the others.
You like her?
No.
You might want to save her.
You okay, sweetie?
It was the most magical place
in the world, wasn't it?
It was.
Another set,
another review.
Another romance,
another breakup.
I'm tired, Fay.
It's okay.
I've been the luckiest bastard in the world.
I had a good run, didn't I?
Hmm?
You sure did.
Yeah. I enjoyed that.
I gotta run, sweetie.
Yep.
It was so good to see you, Fay.
You're gonna do great things
in Europe.
You were always
one of the good ones.
Thank you.
Ciao, my love.
Ciao.
- See you in Venice.
- See you in Prague.
I'm gonna go
get those cigars.
Hey, you do a great job.
What's the best tip
you've ever received?
Fifty dollars.
Who gave you that?
You did, Mr. Conrad.
It's on you now, kid.
The future's yours.
They're looking for us.
Get up.
I don't feel good.
We are going to Mexico,
Nellie.
Mexico?
Get dressed. We are going now.
I'm not going to Mexico.
Are you crazy?
They are going to
fucking kill us, okay?
I fucked up.
Go hit a piñata
if you're homesick.
Nellie, get dressed
and get in the fucking car, now!
Manny, you're scaring me.
I need another hit.
Okay, I feel better.
Oh, hi. Do you have any coke?
Yeah, I've actually got--
Don't give her anything,
pendejo. Anything!
Fine, I won't!
Get everything you need.
We get gas.
See you in ten minutes, cabrón.
Ten minutes.
And some pills, please?
Stop it.
Stop messing with the--
Suck a dick, Señor Avocado.
We need a fucking
gas station, now.
"We need a gas station, now."
Yeah, we fucking need--
"Blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah."
There!
There's gas.
Fuck! ¡Puta madre!
It's closed.
I know it's closed!
You know what we should do?
We should go dancing!
Manny! Oh, my--
We could dance up here.
Manny! Manny, come up here.
Manny! Come on, it's fun.
No, it's not fun.
Yes, it is.
It's not fun.
We can have fun.
Nellie?
Nellie!
Maybe they got dancing here!
Come on!
Nellie.
Nellie!
Manny!
Nellie,
we have to leave now!
I'm staying, Manny.
I'm not moving.
No, no, no, no.
You know what happen
if they find us.
Why are you doing this,
carajo? Why?
Manny, I shouldn't...
I shouldn't have
asked you to help me.
Let me help. I want to help.
We can go to Mexico, Nellie.
And we can be happy.
But we have to leave now.
Manny. Manny.
It's the end of the road for me.
This is it for me.
Cállate.
It's not.
I'm at peace with that.
I'm not mad anymore.
Manny...
Nellie, cállate.
You go to Mexico without me.
What the fuck I'm gonna do
without you? I'm not going
anywhere without you!
Manny...
Te amo.
Te amo, Nellie.
What have I done?
I don't think
I'm good for you.
I'm very good for you.
Nellie, I want to marry you.
I want to make you so happy
every day.
Okay, it's my only job.
From now on.
But we have to leave now.
Okay.
I just want to be with you.
Okay, we'll...
We'll go to Mexico.
We'll go--
We'll go to the border
and we'll go down south
and we'll get married
and we'll have kids and--
It'll be you and me, okay?
Okay.
Te amo, Nellie.
I love you, Manny.
Hey, you two with the camera!
Do you know who I am?
I'm Nellie LaRoy, bitches.
Holy shit, that is Nellie LaRoy.
That's Nellie fucking LaRoy.
Come here.
This is my husband-to-be,
Manny Torres.
Wait. Sorry?
We're gonna get married.
We're gonna get married?
Are-- Are you really
gonna be her husband?
Yes. Yeah.
Congratulations!
Get a shot.
Get it, get it, get it.
Do you need anything?
You go grab him.
I'm good.
Te amo, Nellie.
I love you, Manny.
Ain't life grand.
Hey. Hey.
I'm sorry.
It was hard to find gas.
Yeah, well,
I got everything we need.
This is my roommate, Kyle.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You need anything?
I'm gonna fill this
real quick.
No, gracias. Let's go.
No. No, no, no, no.
No. No, no.
Don't kill me.
Please don't kill me.
I'm nobody. I'm nobody.
Que soy mexicano.
I can leave. Please, please.
I'm sorry.
Get the fuck out of LA.
Disappear.
Nellie. Nellie?
Nellie?
Nellie!
Nellie! Nellie!
Oh, fuck!
And introducing tonight,
a new addition
to the Hart Café Band.
Fresh from pictures,
Mr. Sidney Palmer
on the trumpet.
Hey, Sid.
You want to say a few words?
Thank you, Tom. Um,
I just would like to say to you
how happy I am to be here.
You all are such
a beautiful, lovely crowd.
So thank you.
If I can, I'd like to, uh,
play something
that I used to play
back in-- back in the days.
I hope you all enjoy it.
Passes, sir?
We're just looking.
Thank you.
Hola. Hi.
It's okay.
Yeah?
Adios.
Bye.
Fifty cents.
Thank you.
Tell me why.
- Why?
- Yeah, tell me why.
I don't know, uh, why.
I just want to be part
of something bigger.
To be part of
something important,
something that lasts,
that means something.